http://www.autismnz.org.nz/terms-and-conditions/

Living with autism
Diagnosis guideUnderstanding autismSupport from usWhat is autism
DefinitionsTraits and characteristicsEducation
ProgrammesEducation teamGovernance
Board of TrusteesConstitution and structureCharitable objectivesAbout us
About Autism New ZealandOur historyMeet the teamResources
Local resourcesCommunity linksIn the news
Terms & Conditions
01. Terms & Conditions These terms and conditions apply to the use of this website. You need to read these terms and conditions. We will use the phrase "these terms" to cover all of these terms and conditions and any changes to them. Read Terms
By using this website, you acknowledge that you are bound by these terms. If you don't accept these terms, you must not use this website. In these terms:  "You" means the person using this website  "Your" has a corresponding meaning  "We" means Autism New Zealand (or Autism NZ). "Our" and "us" have a corresponding meaning.    Changes to this website  We may change the information on this website, including these terms, at any time. By continuing to use this website after any changes have been made, you acknowledge that you will continue to be bound by these terms.    Errors and updates
We reserve the right to add or remove material, and correct errors. If you find any errors on any part of autismnz.org.nz, please email the National Information Support Coordinator at Autism NZ’s national office on info@autismnz.org.nz.    General information  We will try to make sure that the information on this website is accurate and up to date however, the website makes information available to you as a general information service only. We do not guarantee that the information we provide is reliable, accurate, or suitable for what you may want to use it for. We may discontinue site availability at any time without notice.  We do not guarantee that the website or the server are free of computer viruses or any other harmful components, defects or errors. We cannot guarantee that any defects in the website will be corrected, or that your access to the website will be reliable, uninterrupted or error-free.  We will not assume any legal liability or responsibility for any delays, inaccuracies, failures, errors, omissions, interruptions, deletions, defects, computer viruses or communication line failures, or for any theft, destruction, damage or unauthorised access to your computer system or network.  Before you rely or act on any of the information on this website, you should get independent professional advice.    Liability  You use this website at your own risk. We will not be liable in contract, tort or otherwise for any loss or damage (direct or otherwise) you suffer in connection with your use of this website or of any linked website or your use of, or reliance on, information contained on or accessed through this website or any linked website.  We exclude any condition or warranty that could be implied into these terms (but only to the extent that this is allowed by law).    Hypertext links  This website will contain hypertext links to other websites that are not operated by us. These links are provided for your convenience and interest only. The inclusion of a link does not imply our endorsement of the site or any association with its operators. We will not investigate or monitor the hypertext links to other websites. You link to them at your own risk. We are not responsible for the information contained on any website that you link to from this website. You may create hypertext links to this website. If you do this, you accept that you are responsible for all direct or indirect consequences of the hypertext link. You also agree that Autism NZ is not responsible for any loss, damage, liability, costs or expense you may incur for creating or maintaining the hypertext link. We reserve the right to prohibit links to this website and you agree to remove or cease any link upon our request.    Intellectual property and our other rights  We hold all copyright and other intellectual property rights in this website. You may use the information on this website and reproduce it (electronically or in hard copy) for your personal use only.  In all other circumstances, you must get written permission from us before you use, send or reproduce any of the information on this website.  Privacy Any personal data you transmit to the site by electronic mail or otherwise, will be used by Autism NZ in accordance with our privacy policy displayed on this site.    Donations  When you make a donation through our website (for example, by making a one-off donation), we may ask you to submit certain personal information (such as credit card information) so we can process your donation. We use the credit card information you provide only to fulfil the transaction you requested. If you are a regular donor, we will maintain your information in our customer service records. We also maintain your contact information in our records so we can contact you to provide Autism NZ information and information on additional giving opportunities.    Local laws and regulations  These terms are governed by the laws of New Zealand. By using this website, you confirm that you are not breaching any local laws or regulations existing where you are. Any information contained on this website does not constitute an offer in any jurisdiction other than New Zealand.   Contact us   If you have any questions about this site email the National Information Support Coordinator at Autism NZ’s national office on info@autism.org.nz
02. Privacy Policy  This privacy policy explains which information Autism NZ collects on www.autismnz.org.nz, what we do with it and your rights to correct or change it. See Details
Personal information We only collect personal information if you choose to give it to us. If you submit a registration form or make a financial donation you provide us with personal contact information so we can connect with you to make further arrangements. All information provided will be held in accordance with the Privacy Act 1993. We do use common internet technologies such as cookies on our website, and collect non-personal information to track traffic on our sites to improve our services. This data does not include personal information and is not linked to any personal information you may provide through our website.    Use and disclosure  The personal information you provide to us will only be used for the purposes for which you supplied it, or, in exceptional situations, for other reasons permitted under the Privacy Act 1993. No personal contact information will be supplied to any third party. This privacy policy only relates to our site. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the practices of sites of other organisations and businesses we may link to on our site. Please check the privacy policies on external sites before providing personal information to them or any other third party.    Your right to access information  The New Zealand Privacy Act of 1993 gives you the right to access and correct, update or delete any personal information that we hold about you. Contact us with your request.
03. Disclaimer  The views and opinions expressed on this site are those of the individual authors and not necessarily those of Autism NZ unless specified otherwise.
The material provided is for information only and not to be used for diagnosis or treatment purposes.
The information provided is not a substitute for professional care in the diagnosis, treatment and management of genetic conditions.
Need help or advice? We are here to help.
Diagnosis guideUnderstanding autismSupport from usWhat is autism
DefinitionsTraits and characteristicsEducation
ProgrammesEducation teamGovernance
Board of TrusteesConstitution and structureCharitable objectivesAbout us
About Autism New ZealandOur historyMeet the teamResources
Local resourcesCommunity linksIn the news
